The most important thing is probably to know when your team is playing.
If you've chosen a team, maybe you're new to baseball but you've chosen a team, you've got to know where to find their schedule.
And I will say the easiest place is just to go to their team website.
That'll be the most up to date if times have changed, if venues have changed, if for some reason they've got to flop around the schedule a little bit because there's a concert at some stadium they didn't expect or there's a national emergency that they didn't expect and they've got to switch things around, that team website is going to be the most up to date.
And also it's very important to look at that schedule because let's say you do have kids, you've got to make sure that you have that opportunity to schedule for the summer.
Maybe you can take a week off and go see a series of four or five games against a great team and have that opportunity to kind of show up.
So it's very important to look at the schedule ahead of time and kind of plan it out.
And I will say teams like the Red Sox, Yankees sell out fast so it's important to look at the schedule ahead of time.
If you want to see them, you've got to get those tickets early.
It'll be hard to wait until the last second because most likely it will be sold out.
That's kind of ticketing and scheduling in a nutshell.
But, obviously keep track of that schedule and it's very important.
If you play fantasy sports, another great way to keep track of the schedule.